Uh good afternoon.
Uh before we get started here today, I'd
just like to first recognize the uh
essential workers that have been out in
our community the last five days
uh helping all that that have been
impacted by this ice storm here this
past weekend. It's not lost on me or our
team here, the effort and work that's
going on to help to get this city back
up and running. We know that it's an
ongoing process and we're just thankful
for the people that are working
tirelessly to help.
Well, this is a special day here.
Um, I want to thank everyone for being
here. Uh, we are very excited. It's an
exciting day here for the Tennessee
Titans organization and fan base.
As we as we are set to introduce our new
leader and head coach,
I would like to first thank Amy for our
unwavering support throughout this head
coaching search, as well as Kenneth and
Burke for their belief and trust in our
process.
There's been a lot of time and effort
here spent invested to get to this day
here today. I couldn't have done it
without the help of so many people,
particularly our search committee
that we put together with Chad, Dave,
Dan, and Reggie. Thank you.
You know, when I first met with the
committee, I thought it was important to
clearly define what we wanted in our
next head coach.
Ultimately, what we wanted was a leader
for this football team that could build
a winning culture and connect the entire
building.
We were looking for a leader with high
character, integrity, humility,
a leader with high football IQ and great
great teaching skills.
A leader with clearly defined standards
that had the ability to hold people
accountable in this organization.
A leader with a clear vision,
plan, and process for this team.
A leader with a high level of
organization and detail.
And finally, we wanted a leader that was
relentless
and committed and had a passion for this
job.
After a long extensive search process,
that leader for us was Robert Salah.
I've long admired Robert from afar
competing against his teams over the
years. The one thing that always stood
out to me was his energy and passion
that he exhibited on the field.
And one of the big takeaways for me is I
used to stand pregame on the field and
watch Robert with his players and
sometimes go down after the game and be
on the sideline.
His players loved playing for him. I'm
just thrilled now
that all you guys here, our players
have an opportunity to play for coach
Salah.
I am so excited here to get started to
work to work with him
to build this together into a
championship caliber team that our
Titans fan base can be proud of.
It's an honor to introduce the next head
coach of the Tennessee Titans, Robert
Salah. [applause]
>> [applause]
>> What's up everybody? Um, I'm not big on
I'm going to pull my inner Michael Mike
McDaniel. I'm not a big uh um opening
statement guy, but I do want to thank a
lot of people uh starting with the
Tennessee Tit Titans and especially Miss
Amy for this opportunity. Chad, uh Mike,
it's been an unbelievable experience
just going through this entire process.
uh the San Francisco 49ers, the York
family, the Shanahan family, uh the
fans, just everybody over there. Just so
thankful for the opportunities they
gave. My family, uh just being by my
side, my wife, my kids, my parents are
here, my brother. Uh just thankful for
all of them. Um and obviously, uh the
most important piece to all this, our
players who are all back there. Can't
wait to work with y'all, man. It's going
to be freaking fun. We're going to get
after it day after day. We're going to
get better. We're going to bring a
championship home and it's going to
start with you guys. But, uh, with that
said, I'll I'll open it up to you guys
and, uh, I'm looking forward to this.
>> Good.
>> Great.
>> All right, we'll start Q& A. We'll start
with Teresa over here and then we'll
circle around. Okay, guys. Just raise
your hand and we'll get to all of you.
Okay.
>> Hi, Robert. Uh, Theresa Walker with the
Associated Press. this being your second
time around as a head coach, what's
maybe the biggest lesson that you take
into this second time from your first
chance?
>> You know, I'll be honest, like um there
there's no handbook to a first time at
anything you do, you know, and uh what I
would say the proper question would be
what didn't I learn? You know, and there
there's so much to gain from anytime
you're in in the chair as a head coach
and there's so many learning experiences
that I had. So, um, I can sit here and
talk to you for the next four hours
about all those different things, but I
can assure you that there was tremendous
growth, uh, through the opportunity that
I had with the Jets and, uh, through
that growth, I think I'm more prepared
now than I've ever been, uh, to attack
this position.
>> Hi, Robert. Paul Kohharski, Paul
Koharski from Paul Khorski.com.
Um, can you walk us through a bit your
plan for Cam Ward and how you and Brian
uh expect to get the most out of him
heading into his second year and into
his career?
>> No, absolutely. Great question, too. you
know, like Cam um from everything that
I've gathered, just all all the
discussions I've had throughout the
building and throughout the league, um
comes with an elite work ethic, uh elite
character, um an elite person, and um
you know, when when you look at his body
of work as a rookie, a lot of these
rookies when they come in, they come in
through the middle of OTAAS, but so the
biggest thing that we're going to work
with Cam just going all the way back to
the beginning. uh you know, we've gotten
a whole off seasonason to work with him.
Take him back to the very very beginning
both on the field, off the field, the
process at which uh uh what it looks
like to not only be a professional with
regards to preparation in his body, but
as a professional with regards to uh um
um preparing from a a game planning
standpoint or a playbook standpoint, but
you know, just work talking with Daves
over the course of the last few weeks,
um he is the perfect man uh to to match
up with Cam and to maximize who he is.
Uh, so again, we're really pumped to to
get to work with Cam and uh get him to
where we all know he can be.
>> Robert Jim Jim White with Tennessee
Titans.com. What do you want your team
to look like on Sundays? What do you
want them to be known for week in and
week out?
>> Fast and violent, man. Um, play in and
play out. Uh, we're going to play with
speed. We're going to play confident.
We're going to have some swag. Talk a
little uh
but uh but I want them to I want them to
show who they are play in and play out.
And like I said, the one thing that
you'll notice is the speed at which we
play and the violence at which we do it.
>> Robert Terry McCormack, Main Street
Media Publications,
wanted to talk to you about ask you
about Brian Dball and how much control
you're going to give him of the offense
and what what that will look like or
what you want it to look like.
>> You know, um obviously Dabs and I have a
tremendous relationship dating back to
our time in New York. um obviously on
opposite sidelines but great empathy for
one another and um uh just going through
those experiences but you know whenever
you look at the dynamics of a head coach
with his offensive coordinator defensive
coordinator um obviously it's no
different than kind of the way Kyle kind
of handled me as a defensive
coordinator. You know there's full
autonomy with regards to game planning
and and making uh putting together the
playbook and and the scheme that's best
for this set of this group of players.
But at the same time, there's going to
always going to be discussion in terms
of what it's going to take between
offense, defense, and special teams.
What type of game plan we need to
formulate in all three phases to win a
football game. And week to week, that's
always going to be different. But uh the
communication, the collaboration, um the
expectations, all those will always be
communicated uh amongst the entire staff
and um uh the idea being that we're
while there is three phases to football,
we're still one team and uh and those
discussions will always be had.
>> Go ahead. Nick Sus with the Tennessee
and uh when you talk about the lessons
you learned from New York, I'm curious,
what are some of the specific things
that you plan to do differently or you
intend to do differently than obviously
the
>> I don't know if we have time, man. Let's
start us off with some big ones.
>> Uh there there's little things, you
know, uh um I don't want to get in great
detail on all that stuff just just to um
just for for sake of uh just
individuality and all that, but you
know, uh ju just one thing and it's such
a small thing. Um you know, I didn't
call plays in uh uh in New York and I I
just kind of gave it all to the
coordinators. Uh even though we were
still part of the game planning and all
that. Um, you know, I I joke with with
Borgo, um, on game day when I didn't
call plays, I felt like I was just a
timeout and red flag guy, you know, I
was just kind of just w I became I had
the the the greatest seat in the house
as a fan, you know. So, um, you know,
calling plays for me, it's not
necessarily about control, but it's
about connecting with the players. You
know, when you are a play caller and you
are calling plays, you feel the strain
that you're putting on them with each
call. Uh, you're feeling the connection.
You're feeling what each one is uh is
going through. And again, like like I
said, I I can feel the weight of the
play call on on individual players in
those moments. And uh to be able to call
plays and maintain that connection,
maintain that uh uh feel for what the
players are going through, I think is
very very important for my seat. And uh
it's just one of the many things that'll
that'll change throughout my tenure.
>> Terron Davenport, ESPN. They call me TD.
Um
>> TD.
>> Yes, sir. TD. Yes.
My question is in regards to Brian Dable
and as you competed against him and you
look back on that, how much did that go
into the like a level of difficulty
going against him? Like how much did
that go into your selection? And with
Dave having the ties to the Hart Perkins
scheme like how much do you feel that's
going to work for Kim?
>> You [snorts] know, I I think it's going
to work great. There's there's a there's
a lot of layers to this one. First off,
you know, um, and
you know, Kyle Shanahan is one of the
biggest best offensive minds in all of
football, period. And if you look at the
NFL landscape right now, his offense and
his influence is all over the league.
Probably, I would argue 80 to almost 90%
of the league. And so Daves is going to
be different, you know. So from a game
planning standpoint, and I'm just
speaking from myself, like as a
defensive coach, you're going through it
just looks like every offense is the
same, but when you play the Tennessee
Titans, it's going to be different. And
so there is a level of game planning
that's going to have to change within a
week. So that's first. Um Daves has had
a history of of uh of of developing
young quarterbacks uh in this league and
college and and the different stops that
he's had and he's touched many from
experience to youth. Uh he's he has a
tremendous amount of experience with
tremendous quarterbacks all over. But uh
um you know there's a lot of benefits to
what he does as a as a defensive guy
game planning against Daves. I can tell
you that he's always going to strain you
both run run and pass. Um he's going to
find the run pass conflicts within your
scheme uh for individual players. He's
gonna attack out of it and uh again,
excuse my language, but uh he's uh he's
special in that regard. He's he he's a
problem to go against.
>> Hi, Coach Sal. Lauren Walsh with WSMV4
here in Nashville. Um, you just
described yourself as a defensive coach
and I think in these coaching cycles we
see a lot of categorizations, offensive
versus defensive types of head coaches.
Do you subscribe to that? And how would
you categorize yourself given somewhat
of a mixture in your background between
the two sides of the ball?
>> Um, I don't. um you know the uh at the
end of the day the the and again I can I
maybe I maybe had a a differentiation I
guess or a thought when I first got a
head job way way back when but after
being in the chair being being in this
chair isn't about offense defense
special teams it's about um it's about
leading not just a group of players but
an entire building and getting everybody
on the same page and doing things in a
way that that help you win on Sunday and
uh so whether you're offense, defense,
special teams in in this particular
chair I don't think It matters.
>> Hey, Coach Chris Harris, also from
WSMV4. We heard Mike talk about the
qualities and leadership he was looking
for at the end of the season. We heard
Jeffrey Simmons talk about how important
a specific type of leader was for this
team. What have you found to be the most
effective way to lead?
>> Um, authenticity. I think, you know,
when you look at player, when you talk
to players, they're grown men. They want
to be treated like men and um and they
want to have discussions manto man, you
know, and uh they want to be they want
to be told the truth. They always want
to be uh know know what they they want
to eliminate gray. They want things
black and white. They want to know where
they stand. They want the truth. Um they
want to be held accountable. Um um but
most importantly, I think they want to
know that you care more about them than
just their jersey number. And I think
that's very important with regards to
connecting with these guys and and
understanding who they are, what makes
them tick um and how to help them
achieve their goals, not just on the
field but off the field. And um and I
think that takes a lot a lot of work
that's beyond the film room. And uh so
when you when you talk about my
leadership qualities, I am it is
important for us to connect with our
guys. It is important to know what makes
them all tick. Um, and most importantly,
obviously, it's it's it's it's our
responsibility as coaches and our
obligation as coaches to help them get
to where they want to go.
>> Hey, Robert. Cory Curtis with News2
[clears throat] here in Nashville. Been
reported that this was the team that
that you circled that you wanted to be
the head coach of. Obviously, there have
been some tough times here the last
couple years. What was it about this
team that you were willing to stake your
coaching future on?
>> Yeah. Um sha uh shamelessly I I I
probably did as much research on this
organization and the people uh the
leadership committee in this uh
organization than they probably did on
me. And uh uh did a ton of research on
on everything I could in terms of um
from top all the way down. And what I
found is that the people here are
unbelievable. Um and and getting a
chance to meet everybody in person uh
just was an affirmation to what I had
already heard. I'm a firm believer that
people win championships. Um, and and
this organization is built to win a
championship because of the people from
obviously Miss Amy all the way down all
the way down. Uh, the people here are
unbelievable and uh um so that that
first and foremost is what drew me close
to this organization.
>> Go ahead.
>> Uh, Buck Buck Rising 1045 the zone. for
you, what stood out about Robert in the
interview and theoretically for both of
you, what stood out about each other in
the interview process that made this
seem like a real fit?
>> Yeah, I mean, like Robert was saying, he
he did a lot of research on us and um we
did a lot of research on you too,
[laughter]
by the way. Um, but a lot of the
research that that we did on Robert um,
from the places he's been, um,
was everything that we were looking for.
When I when I laid out those leadership
qualities,
um, the people that we talked to, he
exemplified all of it. I mean, we called
coaches, we called scouts, we called
players that he had coached before.
Um, and so then when we had the
opportunity to bring him in, um, you
could feel his leadership as soon as he
walked in. He Robert has a presence
about him. Um, and then he was very
thoughtful in everything that he laid
out from the offseason program to
training camp, the way he was going to
do practices.
Um, you know, he's very in tuned in into
in the weight room as well as you can
see. [snorts]
um he just he had a plan for everything.
Player development was a big part of it
and that that was one thing that we
heard over and over again. He can
develop players. Um going through his
plan for player development and things
he does with the coaches uh to develop
his players. Um obviously the scheme
that he's run. I mean he the high
football IQ. Um and then re really the
biggest thing was the the person too.
You know every every person we called
Robert is a great human being. So when
he talks about people [snorts] we want
great people here and
that's a big part of it.
>> So appreciate you man.
>> Yeah.
>> Paul Koharsski. Paul Kuharski again. I I
don't want to kick Brian out before he's
in, but succession plans for successful
offensive coordinators uh have been a
thing here. Um and it's been reported
that you presented uh one if he has the
success that you and the organization
hope for here. Um what what happens from
there and how do you plan for that in
advance? No, we we've really excited
about the staff that we've been able to
assemble over the last week uh uh since
I uh uh since we officially uh uh locked
arms, if you will. But, um there's a
plan, I think, when you look at our
staff and uh obviously there's still
some things that are fluid um before we
announce all of them to you, but we've
got a tremendous mixture of experience
and youth. Um, we've got some young guys
that'll be uh on the offensive staff
that we feel are on the fast track to
becoming coordinators. Um, and like I
said, for me, the succession plan comes
from from my uh from my seat in terms of
what our plan is for each individual
coach and how we develop them. You know,
I've talked about it before. You know,
the the the
most cliche statement a coach can make
is that it's our job to develop players.
It's like, well, no kidding. Of course,
that's our job, but who are the people
developing the coaches who are asked to
develop the players? You can have a
coach in the stone age that's developing
his players, but his players never going
to leave the stone age. So, how are we
keeping our coaches up to date,
evolving, staying ahead of the game, so
our players are constantly evolving and
staying ahead of the game. So, we have a
program for that to make sure that our
coaches are constantly evolving and
pushing the envelope of what they're
capable of. No different than we're
going to ask our players to push the
envelope of what they're capable of. Um,
so to go back to your original question,
there's a plan in place. Um, it'll kind
of be revealed once we start showing off
our uh revealing our coaches. Uh, but it
it goes beyond the name of the coaches
that are are involved. It's going to go
to the development that we expect them
to have.
>> Robert Jill John, Fox 17 Sports. You
mentioned what you want the team to look
like on Sundays on the field. When it
comes to building the culture you want
to see from this team in the locker room
here in Nashville, what are the biggest
keys you want to emphasize when starting
to build those building blocks for the
culture you want?
>> No, you know, again, it goes back to
people, you know, um bringing in people
who are capable of executing the vision
of the entire organization. Um we're
going to preach effort, we're going to
preach strain, we're going to pre preach
violence. Uh we want great character
individuals both on and off the field.
And um and that's where uh Borggo and I
in terms of evaluations is for checking
the box on making sure that these young
men are actually capable of doing that.
That's what builds culture and uh we'll
we'll always maintain that standard. Um
we're going to uh obviously the uh you
know I've always said that the best team
coach teams are the teams that coach
themselves. But in the beginning, it's
going to come from us. And uh at at a at
a certain point, as this team becomes
veteran and it takes off and it
understands what the standard is, the
players will maintain the standard. And
uh and at the end of the day, the
standard will always be the standard.
But um but it starts with people.
>> You've used uh all gas, no breaks, love
and regard. Now what? Uh so to use yours
uh now [clears throat] now what
[laughter]
>> now we'll always be all gas no break man
but um you know it's uh the the the
words are words you know it's always
going to come back to the silent tape
and what we show on tape that's our
resume that's who we are and um you know
so whatever whatever word we use to
identify what we want it's it's all fun
and uh but at the end of the day it's
the tape the tape will always show
everything
>> and I know you got to learn your t learn
this team and watch tape to learn more
about players, but of of the guys you do
know on this roster or what you've seen,
whether it's Jeffrey Simmons, Jim Day, a
couple of Pro Bowlers, what have you
noticed about players that you will have
under you now?
>> You know, we we obviously we uh played
this group a little bit later. U so we
have a have a good feel for for the
young young nuculus that's here and
there's a lot of exciting guys that uh
we're all excited to work with. Um,
obviously there's there's still a lot of
work to do with regards to evaluating
the roster and getting with Borggo and
his staff and uh seeing where we're at,
but um, again, it's it's to be able to
sit here and work with guys like like
Jeffrey and uh, get to work with a guy
like Cam and all the different pieces
around them and um, it's going to be
really exciting to to get this thing
going.
>> Robert, when you talk about establishing
a standard, what will it look like when
the standard is set? How will people be
able to recognize that your standard has
been set?
>> Already said it, man. They're going to
pop off the tape. Uh you're going to
feel like you're on the field with them
with the the energy, the juice, the
speed, the violence. Um you're going to
feel it from the living room sitting on
your couch. You'll be able to feel this
football team.
>> What do you feel like are once you've
got your staff in place are kind of the
first steps to kind of implement
everything and and get things going in
the direction you want it? Man, there
there there's so much to do starting uh
starting the day. I mean, you can call
it Monday um which is the the first
report date for the coaching staff. Uh
but there's a lot of stuff to do from
implementing scheme to evaluating the
roster to uh creating our profile tapes
for Borgo in terms of what each position
should look like to evaluating draft
prospects with Borgo and his staff and
free agency. So, and then obviously
getting our plan set for OTAA. So,
there's a uh a lot of things in terms of
there's going to be a lot of
multitasking in terms of with a new
staff coming in, there's a lot of things
that need to happen. Um, we'll set those
schedules accordingly, but uh there's a
lot of tees and a lot of eyes that need
to be crossed and dotted.
>> Coach Sala, the Courtland Griffin with
the three-point conversion. You you
spoke about connecting with players, but
also setting the standard. How much is
that of that is going to start with the
younger guys like Fiola Dejo, Chim DK,
like you say, Cam and the other guys
when they walk into the building and
meet you for the first time?
>> It it's everybody young, veteran, it
doesn't matter. Um, you know, the second
you walk into this building, the there
there's going to be there's a standard,
there's messaging, there's uh there's an
expectation of what we do both the
second we walk into the building. Um,
you know, I'll say it I'll say it a
million times that the the objective of
life is to go to bed better than when
you woke up. And if you don't have that
intent, if you don't have that mindset,
you're doing yourself a disservice.
You're doing your teammates a
disservice. You're doing your family a
disservice. And um uh so it it doesn't
matter who it is. If you're an employee
of this organization or you are part of
that locker room, the expectation is
that you're finding ways to get better
and uh and that'll that'll always be at
the front of everything we do.
Robert, you mentioned how the all gas no
brakes that those are just words, but
behind those words, there's always ideas
and beliefs and just ways to operate for
you. What is the root of that? Who are
some of the people that have influenced
you to have this high energy approach to
playing football?
>> You know, um I kind of just said it with
with uh you know, all gas, no break.
It's it's not just effort on the
football field. It's it's how you
approach life. uh how you approach
regen, it's how you approach uh lifting,
it's how you approach practice, your
study habits. Um again, and it's really
applies to to anyone in general, applies
to my my wife and kids. You know, you're
you're waking up and you're going to bed
better than when you woke up with an
intent to get better. That's you're that
that is the main focus of all of it. And
I you know, I I've said it before, my my
life completely changed when I got to
Seattle in my early 30s. You [snorts]
know, when you you look at guys like
Pete Carroll, Gus Bradley, Kenny Norton
Jr., uh there's just so many people on
that staff that influenced my life and
not only on the field and for terms of
football, but off uh off the field to be
a better father, a better friend, a
better man, uh was a tremendous amount
of learning for me. Um but Gary Kubak,
uh the Shanahan family, Papa Shanahan,
Monty, I mean, I can go with so many
unbelievable coaches in this league's
history that that have been have had an
unbelievable impact on me. Um, but the
the trigger point for me, I had a a
little three-month-old
um at the time and you know, just trying
to figure out who I was as a person. Uh,
Seattle couldn't have been a better spot
for me.
>> Coach Salah, I don't know if you've
thought this far ahead yet, but do you
plan on running the stairs at Nissan
Stadium, and why, if yes or no?
>> Um,
yeah. Um, no, for sure. Um, I', you
know, I've been doing that since I was
in a GA in college. It's just a way to
kind of burn some steam before the game.
Otherwise, I' i'd be a lunatic. Um but
um but no, it's just a just a habit I've
gotten into. Call it more superstition
than everything. Uh but um but yeah,
plan on it unless it gets too hot out
there, but probably not.
>> All right, Mike Patton uh touring the
AFC South. Um you mentioned wanting to
uh call the plays this time instead of
uh letting the coordinators do so. Uh,
in doing that, are you still going to
be, you know, active in all parts of the
practice with offense and defense,
special teams as well?
>> Yeah. Uh, there there, um, 100% still
being active in all that stuff. Um, plan
on not changing anything with regard to
my role. Um, especially having gone
through it. Um, and just it it it's not
going to be any issue.
>> You talked about authenticity earlier
and having to be yourself.
I think there were times with the Jets
you might have held it back a little
bit. Do you plan on cutting it more
loose this time around?
>> Well, that's part of it, right? Uh what
I'm what I've been uh talking about with
regard to connecting with the players,
you know, what people don't really
realize with these players and the
amount of work that they put in um for
one play. You know, you got a third and
four, fourth quarter critical situation.
a player puts in hours, hours and reps
and there's so much detail that goes
into that one moment. And when that
player executes that moment, what you
see from me is I I become a fan and just
I become their parents, you know, just
their biggest fans and just elated for
that person who just made that play.
That's that's that's what you're seeing.
And um but it takes a connection which
which goes back to why I have this
desire to call play is to to regain that
connection because again you feel the
moment with the player and um but uh but
to answer your question it'll probably
come out more naturally than than
anything.
>> Robert Junior Cooper WSMV4. You
mentioned developing these players. When
you look at the roster and you see how
young it really is. What level of
excitement does it bring you to know you
can kind of get your hands in there and
mold these guys to these high level
players?
>> No, I'm I'm like I said, I think I think
I speak for everyone. You know, we're
we're really excited about the roster.
You can call it a blank C canvas if you
want, but uh but there's also some
veteran leadership that you can't forget
about. Uh there's some really really
cool talent on this football team and um
just excited to get to work with all of
them.
>> Robert, Julian Menzone, News2 Nashville.
Um what would you characterize a
successful first season for you?
>> Um
you know that's always a good question.
You know um obviously every team wants
to win a Super Bowl. Every every team
wants to wants to achieve the pinnacle
of sports that that everybody does. But
but the realistic expectation is that
this team understands what process what
proper prop pro process looks like. Uh
attacking every moment, attacking every
day. Um uh finding ways to get better
every single day. And I I know that's
kind of cliche and kind of boring, but
at the end of the day, we don't have
control over the result of a football
game. It's an oblong football. You know,
you you don't know how it's going to
bounce. But what we have control over is
the way we attack our moments, the way
we attack our day-to-day operation. Uh
the the the the way we build confidence
in our preparation so we can attack the
heck out of Sunday to put ourselves in
best position to get the result we want.
And uh so from a successful stamp, uh
being successful, what that looks like,
I'll leave it up to you guys. But in
this building, it's going to be about
how we attack our moments.
>> Robert,
>> oh yeah. Uh Ben Arthur, NFL on Fox. Um
Robert, you you've talked a lot about,
you know, just how important Well,
you've emphasized multiple times just
how important it is going to be to have
like the right people in the building.
Uh but like a lot of people say that
when they come in as coaches and
whatnot. So, what is it about your
process um that gives you confidence
that you can actually bring in the
people to set the correct tone uh for
the culture in the building?
>> No, that that's a great question. And I
think it takes a tremendous amount of
discipline, you know, like I I I can I
don't want to speak for Borgo, but I can
speak on on my my history and how
enamored we can get with tremendous
length and speed and and all the things
that we think can make an unbelievable
athlete. But at the same time, there's
there's there's a discipline to making
sure that the right people are in the
building first before we go anywhere
else. And uh you know, it's we've we've
we've had a history of it. I can um you
know in terms of bringing in the right
guys and developing the right people but
um like I said I feel like our history
kind of speaks for itself with regards
to the development of these young guys.
>> Mike uh we see Cam back there. Is there
anything you could tell us about his
progress and and uh prognosis? And then
Robert u you know how quickly does Brian
communicate with his quarterback guy?
What can Brian how much can you and
Brian talk to him about what you want
him to do now and and based on the
prognosis, what can he do?
>> Yeah, I I will say that he is um
currently, you know, rehabbing and um I
don't want to give a specific timetable
when he's going to be back, but uh but
he's doing well. He's doing well. Um, as
far as when we can contact, um, you
know, we'll always have friendly
conversations, but, um, you know, there
there's there's different things that we
can do from, uh, um, from a football
standpoint within the within the rules
of the CBA. Um, you know, so we we we
plan on taking advantage of all those.
>> Will Brian talk to his quarterback then?
>> Um, hopefully. Uh, all these are all
things that we've got to discuss over
the next week.
Robert, you mentioned the amount of
research you did on the Titans before
you took the job. What were the
questions that you were looking to get
answers to before you were comfortable
taking the job?
>> Yeah, it's again, it's about people, you
know, just just trying to figure out um
trying to figure out the people, you
know, uh obviously first and foremost,
Miss Amy, you know, and uh uh from
everything I've ga gathered, she's an
unbelievable human and the resources
that she's put into this organization is
is like nothing I've ever seen before.
Uh she's she's for a lack of a better
word putting her money where her mouth
is in terms of how much she loves this
team, how much she loves this city. Um
how much she loves the people in this
organization and uh you know, but
starting with her with uh and and and
working on down to everybody within the
building. It's been uh like I said, the
people here and the conversations I've
had just trying to figure out who's
real, who's authentic, and who's not. um
uh be hardressed to find someone to say
something bad about the people in this
building.
>> Last three, we'll start with [snorts]
TD.
>> You mentioned how important feel for the
game is for you. Where are you as far as
measuring that against an analytics and
we we know it's been a part of the way
people coach tendencies, right? That's
another word for
>> but where are you as far as weighing
those two things against each other?
>> Yeah. Um analytics is just a gathering
of information. we've been doing it
forever, but there's this new age of of
football, right, where there's there's
more numbers, there's more information,
and um I think there's still uh it's all
still within the moment. You know, that
the the new age of football is is really
a new set of information, but it's still
our responsibility to make what's make
the decision that's best for the
football team. It's not as simple as a
book is telling you whether or not to go
for it. Um there's the book doesn't
account for weather. It doesn't account
for whether or not Jeffrey Simmons is up
against their their third string guard.
It doesn't account for any of that. Um
so there's there's still decisions that
need to be made and um and we can get
more detail later on on how I go through
that process, but uh but it's it's
information. It's information that we
welcome and uh but at the end of the
day, we still have to take all that
information and make the decision that's
best for the team.
>> Anything else?
All right, close.
>> Thanks, guys. Appreciate you guys.
[applause]